Sharad has joined us with the Trimurti segment. Let us
know about three stocks and the
news related to them. Sharad, good morning. Tell me,
ICC Lombard will be in focus and here is the
general insurance data of Paytm and
here a lot of strength has been seen in the data.
21% growth of their premium was seen on a unit basis
and this is the second consecutive
straight month in Paytm 24 where strong
numbers are being seen. Apart from this, the
market premium of the overall industry has
gone up by only 18%. This means that the company has
outperformed the industry and has
also outperformed its peers like
your Star Health and National Assurance Make
A Math. The second stock which will be in focus will be
your inside deal space and Adani
Ports, their promoter has acquired about 20
lakh shares
in the month of June. Apart from this, in NIB Bearings, which was recently rallying, the
promoters have acquired ₹16
and in Star Cement also the promoters have
bought about 6.5 lakh shares in the month of June. Apart from this, the
third stock which will be in focus will be Paytm.  If I talk about
Toilet Power and here they have signed a
deal with the Maharashtra Government for hydro projects
and have a capacity of 5700 MW and the
initial investment is going to be
around Rs 27000 crore. There is a
rise in power stocks. We will discuss
Toilet Power, JSW Energy,
both of them. In this, the news of hydro in Toilet is being
reported.
Remember Merchant Pawar's lion in Jio Energy the most at this
time and tomorrow if you look at the intraday, Sir, in the
second half of the D session, there was a tremendous increase in both JSW Energy and Toilet Power.
Look, the band went up to six, around 265
in the last A trade, there is a rise in Toilet Power.
Exactly Santosh,
what levels are being formed in the charts in Toilet and JSW?
Now, at which place do you see more strength? There is
some technical issue. Let's reconnect with
Santosh. Till then, Sumit, you tell me the
levels of JSW Energy and Toilet Power
and where does the strong trade sit.
See, Toilet Power has already given a breakout. If
you look at the last three sessions,  The closing that came yesterday from 50050 to 612 has already
given a good impression of
10 to 15%. But
if we talk about JSW Energy, then it will
still do so at a resistance which is
around the level of 270, so the zone is 270 to 275.
As soon as this is sustained and the level is
crossed, then I feel that a fresh
round of our run will start now. If a
buying opportunity is being created here, then
you can keep a target of 315 and 350. If a
buying opportunity is being created, then
keep 247 as a stop loss. Those who have toilet power,
I would say that there is strong
momentum. You should definitely keep it on hold. The
target expectation in the website is
656 and this bill is for life time.
So if the weekly closing is above 650, then
my suggestion would be that you can
hold it for the next 3 to 4 months also. Let's
talk.  The position is fine for 30-6 months. The
view on toilet power is good, but among the many
decided deals that Sharad was telling, the
Adani Group stock is being watched. There are
about 20 lakh shares in the promoter group of Adani Ports,
in NR bearings also for ₹1
lakh
and in the last one also we have seen a move of 12-15%, so it is
moving so well, that means something more positive can
come, will you
check it once with the chart of I Bill B bearing and tell me, Sumit, should we
still look for an entry point in this
or has it become a little risky, wait for Deep, it is
like resistance, if you look at the weekly closing,
last time also there was a rejection in the stock
in January, in D month,
January 22 and Octopus 22, so this is a level which is
185 to 190, if the weekly closing is A, then
why won't a bank offer be made in it
and the stock will go for its lifetime high, so
my view is waiting here,
if whoever has it, please call it and there is opportunity, yes
Above 190, the
fresh bank is only at 190, now
I will say that it might face some rejection,
but this rejection will be just
like a profit booking, so you should definitely
wait for 1983 but the upset momentum is
in the aside momentum, then if the next
target becomes 2014,
we are not seeing a lot of strength,
it was performing in yesterday's session as well,
but apart from this, if we talk about the non-life insurance
sector, the data has come
and an 18% jump has been seen here on your basis
in the data, so strong major
general insurance data and
ICC Lombard is leading in it, you see yesterday we had a
good rise till about and the latest data is coming
that what
percentage increase has been seen in the premium in it
on an annual basis and for the second time in 5 24 these
figures are strong, I am
satisfied with your opinion on general life insurance, once
start with ICC Lombard,
if we talk about New India Insurance, there is a
lot in their premium also,
after a healthy collection in the stock  It is
clearly visible that the stock had
performed well but now there
is a reversal, I think
1 2 8 6 are seen at 1285, if it
moves above that then perhaps we can see
targets of 1380 1400 in the stock in the coming two days, a
buy
opinion should be kept here, below 1200 15 the stock will
remain plus, auto sector
I think its impact will be seen in the coming time,
insurance data, actually the
insurance data that came yesterday is showing a lot of strength,
so
monthly data will come on all insurance stocks, I will tell you,
keep an eye on it, there may be excitement.